<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VideoClub</string>
    <string name="sign_in_title">VideoClub</string>
    <string name="sign_in_hint">Enter your username</string>
    <string name="sign_in_button_text">sign in</string>
    <string name="sign_in_continue_text">continue as %s</string>
    <string name="sign_in_input_error">Invalid username!</string>

    <string name="home_title">Available movies</string>
    <string name="movie__item_content_desc">Movie thumbnail</string>
    <!-- Movie descriptions -->
    <string name="lotr_description">
            The Lord of the Rings is an epic high fantasy novel written by English author and scholar J. R. R. Tolkien.
            The story began as a sequel to Tolkien\'s 1937 fantasy novel The Hobbit, but eventually developed into a much larger work.
            Written in stages between 1937 and 1949, The Lord of the Rings is one of the best-selling novels ever written, with over 150 million copies sold.
    </string>
    <string name="matrix_description">
            The Matrix is a 1999 science fiction action film written and directed by The Wachowskis (credited as The Wachowski Brothers)
            and starring Keanu Reeves, Laurence Fishburne, Carrie-Anne Moss, Hugo Weaving, and Joe Pantoliano.
            It depicts a dystopian future in which reality as perceived by most humans is actually a simulated reality called "the Matrix", created by sentient machines to subdue the human population.
    </string>
    <string name="matrix_2_description">
            The Matrix Reloaded is a 2003 science fiction action film, the first sequel to The Matrix, and the second installment in The Matrix trilogy, written and directed by The Wachowski Brothersnote.
            It premiered on May 7, 2003, in Westwood, Los Angeles, California, and went on general release by Warner Bros. in North American theaters on May 15, 2003,
            and around the world during the latter half of that month. It was also screened out of competition at the 2003 Cannes Film Festival.
    </string>
    <string name="matrix_3_description">
            The Matrix Revolutions is a 2003 science fiction action film written and directed by The Wachowski Brothersnote.
            It was the third installment of the Matrix trilogy, released six months following The Matrix Reloaded.
            The film was released simultaneously in 60 countries on November 5, 2003. While it is the final film in the series, the Matrix storyline is continued in The Matrix Online.
    </string>
    <string name="inception_description">
            Inception is a 2010 science fiction film written, co-produced, and directed by Christopher Nolan, and co-produced by Emma Thomas.
            The film stars Leonardo DiCaprio as a professional thief who steals information by infiltrating the subconscious, and is offered a chance to have his criminal history erased as payment for the implantation of another person\'s idea into a target\'s subconscious.
    </string>
    <string name="info_movie_image_desc">Movie image description</string>
    <string name="info_movie_reserve">reserve</string>
    <string name="info_movie_category">Category: %s / Copies left: %d</string>
    <string name="action_reservations">Reservations</string>
    <string name="title_activity_reservation">Your reservations</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="reservation_title_paid">paid</string>
    <string name="reservation_title_unpaid">pay</string>
    <string name="reservation_prepay_message">Thanks for prepaying your reservation!</string>
    <string name="info_movie_rating_thx">Thanks for rating!</string>
</resources>
